similar to a la app except that law is
cutting somewhat cut and drive I mean
what actually says it's cut and dry the
interpretation of that is possibly not
kind right but there's a lot of rules we
have in our society that are not cut and
dry there are etiquette rules of what
you should do in this situation
and how you should act and we get mad at
each other for not knowing these
unwritten rules so as someone who maybe
isn't great at recognizing them until
they've been pointed out to me and then
being like okay I can do that some of
the time I would really like it
etiquette guide and I think that at
least shows in the difficulty in doing
it like can ask okay well when you go to
someone's house do you bring a bottle of
wine and 80% of people are absolutely
you'd be rude not to ten percent are
like if they're not alcoholics and I
think 10 percent would be like like oh I
would plant is a better option whatever
it happens to be you're able to
crowdsource the actual etiquette so that
at least when you get angry that
somebody didn't bring a bottle of wine
or that somebody did you're like oh
actually 80% of people agree with it
this is like holding the audience but on
everyday etiquette and then also with
that and similar to knowing laws all
around the world doing the etiquette all
around the world where you know I'm in
Vancouver and one of our local
etiquettes that it annoys among people
who aren't here do and I'm like maybe
they're not from here maybe they don't
know they don't take the schedule is on
the SkyTrain site it's the sky train
escalators especially you walk left and
stand right it is even I don't know if
they're actually at the newer sky trains
but they're definitely at some of the
sky dreams those signs and so because of
that and so many people use the sky
train then becomes customary at any
elevator that would allow two-way
traffic so which you look at stand
beside each other that you walk left is
walk left and right and so yeah just
having a local etiquette guide would
also be wonderful
so that is Apple number seven